<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Vulmon Blog</title>
    <description>Vulmon Blog. Vulmon is a vulnerability and exploit search engine with vulnerability intelligence features.</description>
    <link>https://blog.vulmon.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="https://blog.vulmon.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 14:52:46 +0300</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 14:52:46 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.0.1</generator>

    
      <item>
        <title>Vulnerabilities Used by Stolen FireEye Tools</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Cybersecurity firm FireEye &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fireeye.com/blog/products-and-services/2020/12/fireeye-shares-details-of-recent-cyber-attack-actions-to-protect-community.html&quot;&gt;disclosed&lt;/a&gt; that they have been hacked, and their tools have been stolen by attackers. These tools are used by FireEye for Red Team assessments.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stolen tools may be disclosed by hackers soon. According to FireEye, “none of the tools contain zero-day exploits” and the tools are leveraging well-known CVEs. However, in the case of disclosure of the tools, the popularity of the vulnerabilities used by the tools will be increased among threat actors and exploited widely.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here is the list of vulnerabilities FireEye tools use:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://vulmon.com/vulnerabilitydetails?qid=CVE-2019-11510&quot;&gt;CVE-2019-11510&lt;/a&gt;: Pulse Secure Pulse Connect Secure unauthenticated path traversal&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://vulmon.com/vulnerabilitydetails?qid=CVE-2020-1472&quot;&gt;CVE-2020-1472&lt;/a&gt;: Microsoft Active Directory privilege escalation vulnerability is also known as &lt;strong&gt;Zerologon&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://vulmon.com/vulnerabilitydetails?qid=CVE-2018-13379&quot;&gt;CVE-2018-13379&lt;/a&gt;: Fortinet Fortigate SSL VPN unauthenticated path traversal&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://vulmon.com/vulnerabilitydetails?qid=CVE-2018-15961&quot;&gt;CVE-2018-15961&lt;/a&gt;: Adobe ColdFusion remote code execution vulnerability&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://vulmon.com/vulnerabilitydetails?qid=CVE-2019-0604&quot;&gt;CVE-2019-0604&lt;/a&gt;: Microsoft SharePoint remote code execution vulnerability&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://vulmon.com/vulnerabilitydetails?qid=CVE-2019-0708&quot;&gt;CVE-2019-0708&lt;/a&gt;: Microsoft Windows Remote Desktop Services (RDS) remote code execution vulnerability also known as &lt;strong&gt;BlueKeep&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://vulmon.com/vulnerabilitydetails?qid=CVE-2019-11580&quot;&gt;CVE-2019-11580&lt;/a&gt;: Atlassian Crowd remote code execution vulnerability&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://vulmon.com/vulnerabilitydetails?qid=CVE-2019-19781&quot;&gt;CVE-2019-19781&lt;/a&gt;: Citrix Application Delivery Controller and Citrix Gateway remote code execution vulnerability&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://vulmon.com/vulnerabilitydetails?qid=CVE-2020-10189&quot;&gt;CVE-2020-10189&lt;/a&gt; – RCE for ZoHo ManageEngine Desktop Central remote code execution vulnerability&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://vulmon.com/vulnerabilitydetails?qid=CVE-2014-1812&quot;&gt;CVE-2014-1812&lt;/a&gt;: Microsoft Windows local privilege escalation&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://vulmon.com/vulnerabilitydetails?qid=CVE-2019-3398&quot;&gt;CVE-2019-3398&lt;/a&gt;: Atlassian Confluence authenticated remote code execution&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://vulmon.com/vulnerabilitydetails?qid=CVE-2020-0688&quot;&gt;CVE-2020-0688&lt;/a&gt;: Microsoft Exchange remote code execution&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://vulmon.com/vulnerabilitydetails?qid=CVE-2016-0167&quot;&gt;CVE-2016-0167&lt;/a&gt;: Local privilege escalation on older versions of Microsoft Windows&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://vulmon.com/vulnerabilitydetails?qid=CVE-2017-11774&quot;&gt;CVE-2017-11774&lt;/a&gt;: Remote code execution in Microsoft Outlook via specially crafted URI (phishing) also known as Microsoft Outlook Security Feature Bypass Vulnerability&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://vulmon.com/vulnerabilitydetails?qid=CVE-2018-8581&quot;&gt;CVE-2018-8581&lt;/a&gt;: Microsoft Exchange Server elevation of privilege vulnerability&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://vulmon.com/vulnerabilitydetails?qid=CVE-2019-8394&quot;&gt;CVE-2019-8394&lt;/a&gt;: Zoho ManageEngine ServiceDesk Plus (SDP) unauthenticated file upload&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;script&gt;

var aaa = document.getElementsByClassName(&quot;post__date&quot;)[0];
aaa.textContent=&quot;Dec 12, 2020&quot;

&lt;/script&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
        <link>https://blog.vulmon.com/vulmon/alerts/2020/07/22/vulnerabilities-used-by-stolen-fireeye-tools/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://blog.vulmon.com/vulmon/alerts/2020/07/22/vulnerabilities-used-by-stolen-fireeye-tools/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Introducing Vulmon Alerts: A Proactive Vulnerability Detection Approach</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Cybersecurity researchers discover dozens of new vulnerabilities every day. There were 17980 vulnerabilities published on just NVD in 2019. This means, on average, 50 new vulnerabilities are published daily. In this kind of environment, relying on periodic vulnerability scans has big risks. First, vulnerability scanner companies need some time to update their tools’ vulnerability databases. Then, their customers need some time to apply updates to vulnerability scanners in their environments. In addition to these time losses, if you consider that vulnerability scanning is done periodically (usually monthly), attackers have plenty of time to exploit “new” vulnerabilities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Vulmon Project aims to provide the fastest, most accurate, and detailed information by using vulnerability intelligence methods. &lt;a href=&quot;https://alerts.vulmon.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Vulmon Alerts&lt;/a&gt; is the second online tool of Vulmon Project after &lt;a href=&quot;https://vulmon.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Vulmon Search&lt;/a&gt;. Vulmon Alerts basically makes you aware of newly published vulnerabilities that are of interest to you. With this proactive approach, you can apply critical software updates quickly without waiting for the results of vulnerability scans.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Vulmon Alerts takes advantage of Vulmon infrastructure, which is fed by more than 70 resources. It notifies you when your subscription queries hit a newly published vulnerability and allows you to take action. You can subscribe to any search query you want through the Vulmon Alerts dashboard. The query list below gives an idea about what kind of queries to which you can subscribe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://alerts.vulmon.com/alerts?squery=tomcat&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;tomcat&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://alerts.vulmon.com/alerts?squery=cisco&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;cisco&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://alerts.vulmon.com/alerts?squery=remote%20code&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;remote code&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://alerts.vulmon.com/alerts?squery=injection&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;injection&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://alerts.vulmon.com/alerts?squery=wordpress&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;wordpress&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://alerts.vulmon.com/alerts?squery=wordpress%20injection&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;wordpress injection&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://alerts.vulmon.com/alerts?squery=wordpress%205.1&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;wordpress 5.1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As you can see, queries you can subscribe to are limited only by your imagination and needs. You can subscribe to any query, including, but not limited to, vendors, products, vulnerability types, researchers, or a combination of them. When your subscribed queries hit a new vulnerability, you will get daily e-mails. If daily e-mails are not enough for you, other options are instant slack notifications and API access.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions or feedback, visit the &lt;a href=&quot;https://alerts.vulmon.com/contactform&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;contact page&lt;/a&gt; for contact information.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
        <link>https://blog.vulmon.com/vulmon/alerts/2020/07/22/introducing-vulmon-alerts-a-proactive-vulnerability-detection-approach/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://blog.vulmon.com/vulmon/alerts/2020/07/22/introducing-vulmon-alerts-a-proactive-vulnerability-detection-approach/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Vulmap: Online Local Vulnerability Scanners Project </title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Are software installed at your computer up-to-date? If they are not which vulnerabilities they have? Vulmap is a project to give these answers to end-users and cybersecurity researchers in the fastest way. You can detect vulnerabilities at your computer and their exploits without any installation. The only thing you need to do is running these scripts from the command prompt.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can check the Github page to review the project, which is also accepted by &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/yavuzatlas_/status/1160654191519571969&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Defcon&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.blackhat.com/asia-20/arsenal/schedule/index.html#vulmap-online-local-vulnerability-scanners-project-19251&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Blackhat&lt;/a&gt; conferences.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/vulmon/Vulmap&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://github.com/vulmon/Vulmap&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
        <link>https://blog.vulmon.com/vulmap/2020/07/14/vulmap-online-local-vulnerability-scanners-project/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://blog.vulmon.com/vulmap/2020/07/14/vulmap-online-local-vulnerability-scanners-project/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Introducing Vulmon Search</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Vulnerabilities are published on different platforms and in different formats. This makes it difficult to find vulnerability information and figure out the relationship between this information. Even if you are aware of a published vulnerability, it is very crucial to assess the real risk of the vulnerability. To do that, CVSS scores are essential sources but are not enough. You also need to take into account the exploitation probability of vulnerabilities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://vulmon.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Vulmon Search&lt;/a&gt; is a completely free vulnerability search engine that is developed under Vulmon Project. Since &lt;a href=&quot;https://vulmon.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Vulmon Search&lt;/a&gt; uses Vulmon vulnerability intelligence infrastructure, it provides detailed information that no other tool can do. Vulmon Search aims to give comprehensive vulnerability information through a very simple user interface. You can search for any vulnerability related words on Vulmon Search. When you open a &lt;a href=&quot;https://vulmon.com/vulnerabilitydetails?qid=CVE-2017-5638&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;vulnerability page&lt;/a&gt;, you can access quite a lot of information about the vulnerability from one page. This information includes, but is not limited to, related exploits, GitHub repositories, vendor advisories, user comments and social media trends.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the most important features of Vulmon Search is that it gives vulnerability &lt;a href=&quot;https://vulmon.com/trends&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;trend&lt;/a&gt; information. It is so important for cybersecurity researchers to know which vulnerabilities other cybersecurity researchers talk about. For that reason, security researchers should check the &lt;a href=&quot;https://vulmon.com/trends&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;trends page&lt;/a&gt; of Vulmon Search daily to stay up-to-date.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Feel free to &lt;a href=&quot;&amp;#109;&amp;#097;&amp;#105;&amp;#108;&amp;#116;&amp;#111;:&amp;#105;&amp;#110;&amp;#102;&amp;#111;&amp;#064;&amp;#118;&amp;#117;&amp;#108;&amp;#109;&amp;#111;&amp;#110;&amp;#046;&amp;#099;&amp;#111;&amp;#109;&quot;&gt;contact&lt;/a&gt; for anything.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 01:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
        <link>https://blog.vulmon.com/vulmon/search/2020/07/07/introducing-vulmon-search/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://blog.vulmon.com/vulmon/search/2020/07/07/introducing-vulmon-search/</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
